[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 1 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "8",
        "10",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 5 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "11",
        "13",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 8 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "12",
        "10",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 12 + 9 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "options": [
        "28",
        "30",
        "35",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 3 + 1 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "12",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 10 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "12",
        "19",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 10 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "116",
      "options": [
        "114",
        "116",
        "121",
        "118"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 6 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "74",
      "options": [
        "76",
        "72",
        "74",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 10 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "87",
      "options": [
        "92",
        "85",
        "89",
        "87"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 7 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "42",
        "38",
        "40"
      ]
    }
]